-Good evening.
Terrace House is a show about
six strangers living together,
and we observe how they interact.
All that we've prepared is
a beautiful home and automobiles.
-There is no script at all.
-Yes.
Indeed. Tonight marks the beginning
of our brand-new season.
Terrace House: Tokyo 2019-2020 is here!
Yay!
-The wait is over.
-We're back!
-I've waited for so long.
-I'm so happy!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
We've been waiting longer
than our viewers.
-That's true.
-We've waited patiently.
As you may have gathered from the title,
we're back in Tokyo,
which is our featured location.
We're slated to continue the show
until the summer of 2020,
when the Tokyo Olympics will end.
-Nice!
-Things are bound to get exciting.
This could mean that some of the members
might be somehow involved
with the Olympics.
It's possible.
-Terrace House has a global audience.
-That's true!
-Turns out we're super popular in London.
-In London?
Apparently there's a Terrace House
fan club there.
-Wow.
-I wanna go visit!
I was at an event the other day
with someone who has a British friend
living in the UK.
He told me he had a favor to ask.
He said, "Can you introduce me to Reina?"
-Torichan?
-Oh, me?
Apparently Torichan is super popular
among the British.
-Please do.
-May I?
-Please do, if there are any great guys.
-Great. Glad I have your consent.
Shall we?
-I can't wait--
-I'm far too excited!
I almost don't wanna watch.
Who will the members be?
What will the house look like?
-Yeah, the house!
-I can't wait to see it.
I'm excited!
We may have a new house,
but we still have Shochan. Congrats!
-That's right.
-This role usually changes
-with each new season.
-That's right.
-Thank you for having me.
-Thanks for being here.
Thanks so much.
-Ready to watch?
-Shall we?
-Who will we get to meet?
-Let's do this.
I can't wait!
Wow!
Am I the first one here?
I'm the first to arrive.
Hello.
-Hello.
-Hi.
-Nice to meet you.
I'm Shohei Matsuzaki.
I'm Kaori Watanabe. Great to meet you.
-Watanabe, you said?
-Yes, Watanabe.
-Matsuzaki, was it?
-Yes.
-Pleasure to meet you.
-You as well.
-May I sit?
-Of course, please.
I sat without asking.
-Nerve-racking, isn't it?
-I'm very nervous.
I've been feeling nauseous...
-this whole time.
-I get that.
Crazy.
-How old are you?
-I'm 28.
-Twenty-eight.
-How about you?
-I turn 26 this year.
-Twenty-six. I see.
What do you do for a living?
Until recently,
I was living in Taiwan.
While I was there, I worked as a model.
I occasionally act in Japan, too.
SHOHEI MATSUZAKI, 25
ACTOR
I also have part-time jobs.
-Yeah.
-I see.
And what do you do?
I didn't mean to pause for so long.
I work as an illustrator, making art.
What kind of art?
I mainly produce work
for fashion magazines...
KAORI WATANABE, 28
ILLUSTRATOR
...so I mostly sketch people and apparel.
-I'd like to see your work later.
-It'd be my pleasure.
-...have a chance to see--
-Hello.
-Hi, there.
Here we go.
Pleasure to meet you. I'm Haruka Okuyama.
Only three of us so far?
-Just the three of us.
-Yeah, so far.
-How old are you?
-I'm currently 24.
-Twenty-four.
-And you?
-I'm 28.
-Twenty-eight.
-And you?
-I'm 26.
-We're all two years apart.
-That's true.
There's even a pool?
-Yeah, there's a pool!
-Can you swim?
I can, but...
I forgot my bathing suit.
It's still pretty cold.
That's understandable.
I didn't think there'd be a pool.
What an enormous house.
Is this close to home for you?
-It's very far for me.
-Oh, it is.
-Super far.
-I came here from Taiwan.
You've lived in Taiwan? You're Taiwanese?
No, I'm not.
Oh, right, since your name is Matsumoto?
-It's Matsuzaki.
-Oh, right, Matsuzaki.
I wasn't enunciating clearly.
Because you speak Taiwanese?
Oh, that's not what you meant?
No. Just by nature.
Why were you in Taiwan?
-I'm a big fan of Taiwanese movies.
-Yeah.
It's always been a dream of mine
to live there.
I made friends there and found a house
around the same.
So I thought,
"I'll just go ahead and move."
And you went for it?
-Wow, that's cool.
-Bold, isn't it?
It's relatively close to Japan.
-Were you based in Taipei?
-That's right.
-Miss Okuyama, what do you...
-"Miss Okuyama"?
What do you do for a living, Miss Okuyama?
At the moment, I'm modeling and acting.
HARUKA OKUYAMA, 24
ACTRESS
From 15 to 20,
I was mostly working as an actress.
-That's a long time.
-Yeah.
You have really great eyebrows.
-Don't you think so?
-I agree.
I'm glad you think so. I used to
get picked on because of them.
They're great. I'm trying to grow
mine out, but it's taking a while.
-Someone's here.
-Someone's here!
-Nice to meet you.
-Great to meet you!
Pleasure to make your acquaintance.
I'm Kenji Yoshihara.
-Great to meet you.
-Pleasure to meet you.
-What do you do?
-I'm a musician.
My band is called SPiCYSOL,
and I'm the vocalist.
Do you do live shows?
-I had one last night, actually.
-I'd love to come watch.
-Definitely.
-Please do.
Do you play guitar?
Yes, that's my guitar.
-Guitar, huh?
-He's a guitarist.
I perform under the name "Kenny."
-Then Kenny it is.
-Kenny sounds good.
-Great.
-How old are you?
-I'm 31.
-Older, then.
KENJI YOSHIHARA, 31
MUSICIAN
-I'm probably the oldest.
-You're right.
What was your motivation
for coming to Terrace House?
I think it's difficult
to date publicly in Japan.
I agree. Romance often happens in secrecy.
Personally, I'd like to be forthcoming
about my love life.
I also hope to start a family soon.
So you're prepared to showcase
the process to get there.
Yeah, you got it.
What do the two of you do for work?
I'm an illustrator.
-What? For real?
-I sketch for a living.
-What were you expecting?
-I'm not sure.
Actually, I draw, too.
Oh, really?
I've been thinking I'd like to do that
professionally as well.
-Let's chat.
-I'd like to pick your brain.
What kinds of things do you draw?
You could call it
"girls you'd find by the ocean."
-Interesting.
-That's my thing right now.
-I wanna see.
-Yes, please show us.
Stuff like this.
Wow! Very nice.
-You're really good.
-I see.
-Stuff like this.
-That's super cute!
Impressive.
Amazing. Also, check out this layout.
It goes with the music.
-Amazing.
-Intricate, isn't it?
Shohei-kun... what do you plan to do
now that you're back in Japan?
-Now that I'm back?
-Same kind of stuff?
Yeah. I'd like to establish myself here.
That's the idea.
What's your part-time gig?
I work for a place
that finishes interiors.
Like painting the interior of buildings?
Yeah. Sometimes demolition,
but also painting walls.
-I'm often disciplined at work.
-I hear another set of wheels!
Someone's coming.
-Nice to meet you.
-She's cute.
-Very cute.
Can I sit?
-Please.
-Wherever you'd like.
Would you like the middle?
Excuse me. Thanks so much.
Nice to meet you! I'm Risako Tanabe.
Risako-chan.
-That's right. Hello, I'm Risako.
-Nice to meet you.
-Pleasure to meet you.
-Great to meet you.
-How old are you?
-I'm 21.
-So young!
-Twenty?
Twenty-one, not 20.
-You seem mature.
-Not at all.
I'll probably look to everyone
for guidance from time to time.
-Likewise. Don't mention it.
-We probably all will.
What do you do for a living?
I work as a fitness trainer.
RISAKO TANABE, 21
FITNESS TRAINER
Recently, I've picked up this sport
called parkour,
and I'd like to do more work
involving that as well.
-Parkour, as in leaping off of objects?
-That's right.
-Have you seen it?
-I know of it.
It can involve jumping between buildings.
My skills aren't quite there yet, though.
So you jump without using any equipment?
Correct. It's all about clearing obstacles
with controlled movement.
-Kind of like ninja training?
-Very similar.
-You leap around the city, right?
-I think I've seen it on Instagram.
They jump all over the place. Awesome.
What were you discussing before I arrived?
What were we talking about?
Our motivations for coming here.
In my case...
and this might be totally my fault,
but there seems to be a trend
where my partners give up on me
because they feel I'm overbearing.
-So far, at least.
-With romance?
Do you mean you're too people-pleasing?
At times too eager to please,
and at other times, too avoidant.
I don't intentionally keep tabs,
but my partners often turn out
to be different once I get to know them.
So I'd like to meet someone special here.
I understand.
Pardon me...
I hear wheels approaching.
-Hello! Nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
-Pleasure to meet you.
Excuse me.
Nice to meet you, everyone.
I'm Ruka Nishinoiri.
It's Ruka Nishinoiri.
-Ruka, okay.
-Ruka-san!
-Pleasure to meet you.
What do you do for a living?
I work part-time in fashion retail.
-How old are you?
-I'm currently 20.
-Close to my age.
-You're the youngest.
RUKA NISHINOIRI, 20
PART-TIME RETAIL EMPLOYEE
-You're the youngest.
-There are no teens.
So you can drink alcohol?
-I can drink a bit.
-We all can, then.
Nice. I brought Taiwanese beer
as a souvenir.
-Really? That's awesome.
-Yay!
I was concerned
there might be someone under 19.
What was your motivation
for coming to Terrace House?
I'm not a great conversationalist.
I'm especially awkward
when speaking to women.
My face turns red.
I'm hoping to overcome that
while I'm here.
I came here to try
to challenge myself with that.
-Let's overcome that.
-Yes.
-That's so cute.
-Totally.
Sorry, we already covered
a lot of the basics before you arrived.
Okay, I understand.
-We haven't seen our rooms yet.
-You're right, we haven't.
KAORI WATANABE, 28
ILLUSTRATOR
SHOHEI MATSUZAKI, 25
ACTOR
HARUKA OKUYAMA, 24
ACTRESS
KENJI YOSHIHARA, 31
MUSICIAN
RISAKO TANABE, 21
FITNESS TRAINER
RUKA NISHINOIRI, 20
PART-TIME RETAIL EMPLOYEE
Crazy.
Whoa!
-Shall we start here?
-The play room!
Play room. Hope it's ready.
-Wow. Cool!
-Nice.
-The infamous play room.
-Check out this TV.
Whoa.
Crazy.
Cool.
These cushions are so fluffy, too.
I could fall asleep.
I could totally fall asleep
while watching a movie.
-Wow.
-Whoa.
So fancy!
Amazing.
It reminds me of a sauna.
A sauna? Yeah, I can see that.
-It's so chic.
-It really is.
-It'd be nice to eat out here.
-Breakfast!
-I wanna do that.
-Let's eat out here soon.
-And now for the guys' room.
-Let's go.
-I've been anxious to see it.
-Me, too.
Here we go!
-Wow.
-This place is huge!
-Nice.
-This is amazing.
There's so much space.
-This bed is so cool.
-This is great.
Cool design.
-This bed is crazy.
-Nice.
-It's a "T" shape.
-Tons of space.
How should we divvy up the beds?
What's the plan?
Go ahead. Youngest gets first dibs.
-I get to choose first?
-Yeah, since cohabitation is new to you.
Really?
"Cohabitation"?
I'd like the top bunk.
-Oh, for real? Great.
-Yeah, I want the top.
I'm truly okay with whichever.
-Can I take the bed by the window?
-Of course.
All right. I'll take the window, then.
Thank you.
I can't wait to see the girls' room!
Me neither.
-May I do the grand reveal?
-Please!
The door says "Girls' Room."
What? Wait...
That was loud! You scared me.
-Wow!
-It's too cute.
It's way too cute.
So it's one, two, and three?
Wow, I can't handle this cuteness.
And look out here!
-An outdoor seating area.
-Another place to eat.
A spot to chill out. This is too cool!
-I like this spot, it feels like an attic.
-It really does.
-Shall we split up the top bunks?
-Let's.
-Which do you prefer?
-I don't have a preference.
-Which would you like?
-I don't mind either.
In that case, I'll take the thinner side.
Kaori over here...
and I'll take the right bunk.
Yeah, sounds good.
-This is great. So cute.
-Agreed.
-Is the lower level visible from here?
-Looks like it.
I noticed that, too.
-It totally is.
-The lower level is wide open.
That means we can spy
-when people have intimate meetings.
-We can see everything.
-We can watch.
Honestly, all three of them are cute.
That's a good start.
Did anyone catch your eye?
Based on first impressions,
I like the girl...
with the long hair. The tall one.
-The one in the middle?
-Yeah, her.
I recall everyone besides Risako
being very tall.
Not the one with the short hair.
So far, the girl with the short hair
caught my eye.
I feel like we'd have a lot to talk about.
That's true.
They all seem very grounded.
-They seem kind and sincere.
-Yeah, it's great.
Were you able to sleep last night?
Slept like a baby.
-I couldn't sleep at all.
-Me neither.
You arrived in Japan yesterday?
I flew in yesterday
and couldn't sleep a wink.
I got home late because of work.
Do you work somewhere
other than Murasaki Sports?
No, I only work there.
I briefly worked for another company
after high school,
but I decided to quit and started working
at Murasaki Sports this year.
So I've only been there
for about four months.
Oh, I see.
And you're searching
for a part-time job, Shohei?
Well, there's the company
that I used to work for
that does interior finishes
and demolitions.
So you'll start work there again tomorrow?
Probably not tomorrow,
but I am planning to reconnect with them.
What was his name,
the one who works in retail?
-I forget his name.
-Ruka-kun.
Yeah, that's it.
Ruka's kind of cute, right?
-He's cute.
-Yeah.
Apparently he can't talk to women
without turning red.
Yeah. He was already visibly red.
-Who did you find the easiest to talk to?
-The easiest?
Matsuzaki, was it?
-The guy from Taiwan?
-Yeah, that one.
I thought so, too.
Kenny is very reserved, isn't he?
He is.
I wonder if our romantic interests
will overlap. Hopefully not!
-That could cause some problems.
-It could.
That's true.
What's your type?
Someone funny and...
-A fun guy?
-Yeah. Don't you love a fun person?
Yeah, I agree. Someone easy to talk to.
-What about you?
-Well...
Someone who laughs a lot. And...
someone with a big love.
"A big love"?
-Someone with "a big love"?
-How should I say this?
Someone with "a big love"?
Someone who helps me feel secure.
Who will always remind you
that he loves you?
-That's nice. Well, I hope he's here.
-That'd be nice.
-Here we go!
-How interesting.
We got the full scope
of our gorgeous cast.
Gorgeous ladies and gents.
-What's this applause for?
-Our joy exploded into applause.
-Amazing.
-We now have our full cast.
-They're a glamorous bunch.
-Very glamorous.
They might be
the most glamorous group yet.
Ultra glamorous.
I didn't see any members
that seemed sleazy or lazy.
-There doesn't seem to be any.
-Agreed.
Do women like that
"I turn red when I speak to women" type?
-He's only 20, so it's adorable.
-Undeniably adorable.
Could he really be so good-looking
yet so inexperienced?
Well, he was actually turning red.
-He was turning pink.
-He did seem bashful.
It's those eyes. Remember this expression?
He smiles with his eyes.
A person who smiles like that
could never be bad.
I agree.
-So cute.
-I want to find that person now.
-Hold on, find who?
-A swindler who smiles with crinkly eyes.
-They do exist.
-Definitely.
Maybe.
There are people
who have that crinkly smile
and are clearly up to no good.
Definitely. Like the comedian
Shinji Mizuta from Wagyu.
I'm hoping to see a battle of the egos
-between Haruka and Risako.
-It could happen.
Kaori seems like she could get caught
in a difficult position between them.
She seems sensitive to everyone's needs.
Actresses tend to be strong-willed.
They tend to think
very highly of themselves.
-Like that incident with Natsumi.
-Yes, just like that.
-She does remind me of Natsumi.
-Agreed.
-I see that, too.
-Very reminiscent.
The battle of Haruka versus Risako...
Both of their hairstyles
seem easy to grab hold of.
Risako seems like
she'd be vocal about her feelings.
-Blunt.
-I can see that.
-I see potential in Ruka as well.
-What do you mean?
I think he could be a problem child.
-Could he be?
-Yeah.
The fridge is empty.
-Not even condiments.
-Guess we have to go shopping.
-Good point.
-Right?
We'll have to grab some essentials
and groceries.
I wanna go shopping.
-Me, too.
-Go for it.
I don't feel like shopping.
We don't have any condiments.
-Yeah, like soy sauce...
-Can I just pick out an assortment?
-Yes, please.
-By all means.
What do you need to make lu rou fan?
I'll do the shopping
when we're ready to make lu rou fan.
-You can cook?
-The ingredients are tricky... Yeah.
-So you can handle that later.
-Yeah. I'd need to go to Chinatown.
-All the way to Chinatown?
-So official.
I need a specific type of soy sauce
for the dish.
-Interesting.
-Cool.
-Shall we get going?
-Time to get ready?
Yeah.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
-Do you drive regularly?
-I do drive a lot.
I'm really into cars.
-Would you recognize a Corvette?
-I don't know much about them.
They're like...
sports cars that are low to the ground.
That's what I drive.
We get to drive Jaguars this season.
-These cars are cool, aren't they?
-Yeah.
Should I wash this, too?
-This thing... I'm not sure.
-What's that for?
Oh, this thing?
-For forks and--
-This'll come in handy.
Are there spoons and other utensils?
There are.
Oh, look what we have here.
I brought souvenirs.
Wow! So much stuff.
-It's Taiwanese beer.
-From Taiwan.
-Thank you so much. Yay!
-Thank you.
You're so quiet, Ruka.
I was absorbed in my task.
What's the extent
of your awkwardness with women?
The extent?
I mean, I'll reply if I'm spoken to.
You were speaking a moment ago.
-You don't start conversations often?
-Not really.
Your face has been flushed
this whole time.
-Am I red?
-You're super red.
-Really?
-It's crazy.
How long have you been drawing?
I began drawing for a living
about two years ago.
But I've always enjoyed sketching.
What style do you draw in?
-I'm curious to see, too.
-Agreed.
You wanna see?
Have you heard of Fudge magazine?
-I think there's a men's edition, too.
-I recall a men's Fudge.
-That's the one.
-What does "fudge" mean?
I designed this
as well as a men's version.
-Of this design?
-Yeah.
-Oops! Sorry.
-No worries.
I designed those
in collaboration with the magazine.
All sketches of people.
-So detailed. Looks great.
-Those were pretty detailed. Thank you!
Sorry, did that sound authoritative?
-No, not at all.
-So cool.
It's great that you support yourself
with this.
I don't have anything under my belt yet.
-That's because you're so young.
-You're 20, right?
Lately, I've mostly been staying home
and playing video games.
I play a lot of games
with my younger brother.
Who else is in your family?
-My family?
-There's you, and...
There's my younger brother
and younger sister,
then an even younger set of twin sisters.
I see! And they're in fourth grade?
Correct.
They just entered the fourth grade.
Do you have siblings?
-I'm an only child.
-Just you, huh?
Do you have any siblings?
I have a brother who's five years older.
-Five years older than you?
-Yeah.
We look exactly alike. A spitting image.
Why did you decide to come
to Terrace House?
I want to grow as an illustrator,
so I want to be around others
who are also chasing their dreams.
Around people who are working hard
toward their goals?
And I just happened to be single
when I applied.
Oh, okay. I see.
This tangerine juice is super yummy.
-You've had it before?
-Yeah, I have.
So the veggies are out here. Got it.
And the bananas.
Yay, bananas!
SHINANOYA GROCERY
SETAGAYA, TOKYO
-Here's a cart. Do we need a basket, too?
-We do.
Thank you.
-Do you cook from scratch?
-Hmm?
-Do you cook a lot at home?
-I cook all the time, yeah.
-I guess medium-hot will work, right?
-Yeah, to start?
Since we're not sure who can handle spice
and who can't.
Risako seems like
she wouldn't be able to handle spice.
I agree.
"It's too hot!"
Ruka doesn't drink much alcohol.
Hold on, we need to grab
green tea for Ruka!
-Oh, yeah, we need loose-leaf tea.
-It's right there.
-He wanted to brew tea, right?
-Right.
Are we missing anything else?
I don't think so,
but I can't really remember.
-And they don't carry two-liter bottles.
-No way!
-Should we go with the bottled tea?
-Let's just say we couldn't find it.
Let's do that.
I don't trust this selection.
-Yeah.
-Okay.
Huh?
They disappeared again.
I'm ravenous.
-Me, too.
-Same.
-It's been a while--
-We're home.
-Welcome back!
-Welcome back.
-You bought so much stuff.
-Awesome!
-Yeah, we bought a lot.
-You got it?
That's a lot of bags.
-Crazy.
-So much stuff.
-Here, I guess.
-Here?
Perhaps over here
would be more convenient.
Heave! Heave!
There really is a ton!
Thanks for picking everything up.
-All right, let's get cooking.
-Yeah.
My eyes hurt.
That must be a good onion, then.
-I guess so. My eyes are burning.
-It must be super fresh.
-It's smoking heavily.
-Whoa...
We forgot to pick up pepper.
-Yeah. We forgot salt, too.
-Oh, well.
It won't even mix.
This pot is too small.
-This won't work!
-Should we sauté half of it in a pan?
What should I work on?
-I'm throwing together a salad.
-Thanks.
-Is that okay?
-Yeah.
-Great.
-I guess I'll slice the cheese.
-Oh, we do have salt and pepper?
-Yeah.
Doesn't this look great?
-Perfection!
-Should I add more beans?
-That looks great!
-It does look yummy.
Shall we?
-Thank you for cooking.
-Yay!
-Thank you so much.
-Thank you.
This really looks great.
Well, happy to meet everyone.
Pleasure to meet you!
-Cheers.
-Cheers!
-Delicious.
-Tasty.
-It's kind of sweet, right?
-Yeah.
-Yummy.
-Tastes great.
-I was so hungry.
-So good.
The curry is delicious.
-It's great, isn't it?
-It's so good.
What did you chat about
while you were doing dishes?
We were seeing in real-time
how red Ruka's face gets
when talking to girls.
He was definitely very red.
-He really did turn red?
-Yep.
So you've never dated before?
-I have.
-So you'd turn red all the time?
No, I'd get used to them.
-Oh, you'd acclimate.
-Yes.
I almost spat out my food.
Your face is red as we speak, isn't it?
-Because of the beer, right?
-Yes.
-The alcohol and the women.
-But you drank so little!
Right.
I turn red easily.
-So cute.
-His neck...
You're bright red around the neck, too.
You seem popular
with older and younger women alike.
Probably more with older women.
-Which do you appeal to more?
-I've never dated an older person.
-Is that right?
-You've only dated younger?
Yeah, either younger or the same age.
-Are you averse to dating older?
-No, not at all.
-What's your preference?
-That grin, though!
Which are you honestly more interested in?
Older women.
-I get that.
-That's what I thought.
It seems obvious.
-It is really that obvious?
-Is it?
Don't men generally prefer older women?
-Is that true?
-I like both.
You mean you just like women.
What's your type?
Like, someone who wants to be
stay-at-home?
Or whatever comes to mind for you.
-No, I mean, that's what I want.
-Oh, I get it.
Someone who could offer emotional support.
In the traditional sense, like fades
to the background and cheers you on?
That's appealing as well.
-You think so?
-That's perfect, huh?
Or someone who doesn't try to get in touch
when I'm out drinking with friends.
I also wouldn't butt in
when she's out and about.
-Ah. You wouldn't, either.
-You'd let each other be.
You don't get jealous?
-Not really.
-You don't?
-That seems a bit lonesome.
-Yeah, I wouldn't like that.
I'd want him to be jealous.
-At least a little bit.
-I feel like I hear that from women often.
-Do you get jealous?
-I get super jealous, so...
-I can see that.
-Totally. It really affects me.
-"Where are you? What are up to?"
-I'd reach out immediately.
I often say that kind of thing.
-For real?
-Yeah, like...
For example, if my girlfriend and I
were watching a movie together
and she started gushing over some actor...
it would irk me.
-Like, "What about me?"
-Cute.
I'd ask if she thought I was cute, too.
-That sounds nice.
-That's funny.
I get jealous easily.
Jealousy does happen.
-It does?
-Yeah.
-What about you, Ruka?
-I get pretty jealous, too.
-You do, huh?
-Yes.
Do you think a ten-year gap
makes a big difference
in how we view romance?
-Does it?
-I'm not sure.
Imagine if we were ten years old.
Kids fall in love instantly.
That's the same age gap, isn't it?
From Kenji's point of view.
When I think back to my teens,
I probably did get jealous quite often.
Since turning 28,
feelings of jealousy have disappeared.
-Really?
-How old were you, again?
-I just turned 28.
-So mature.
Does it become easier to let go?
You start to want to support
that person's individual interests.
I think your values change.
She might be a good support for you.
-I look forward to building a partnership.
-She would support you!
Will you guys be busy
after we all settle in?
My schedule will pick up next week.
-With recording.
-You mentioned that.
-Will you be busy, Shohei?
-Not at all.
You're free until you find part-time work?
I'm planning on contacting
my old workplace.
You have work, right, Ruka?
Yeah, I have my part-time job.
Three times a week.
But in two days,
I'll have a three-day weekend.
Great timing.
Are you gonna ask someone out?
Hmm. I guess I should.
I want to ask Kaori out.
Kaori has a unique vibe.
-She doesn't talk about herself much.
-That's true.
-It's intriguing.
-You've been observing her.
And you, Ruka?
I...
-You were interested in Haruka, right?
-Yeah.
You guys seemed to be
hitting it off at dinner.
But it's not particularly easier
to talk to her than the others.
I see.
You're both still in your own bubbles?
Yeah, there's a bit of that happening.
-But you wanna get to know her better?
-I do.
-Haruka, right?
-Yes.
I feel like I could learn a lot
by spending time with her.
So, what do you think?
Their personalities are all very distinct.
Completely different types!
I can't get over how adorable Ruka is.
-So cute. His every action.
-He's super cute.
I enjoy seeing his adorableness.
It's like watching a cute little creature.
I can't help but watch him.
So, Kenny.
He was easy enough to chat with
when we went shopping together,
but I can't get a read on him.
Is it just his maturity--
-It's like he has a wall up, right?
-Yeah. I sense that.
I'm the closest to him in age,
but I feel that wall, too.
He's unique.
Yeah. I can never tell what he's thinking.
As for Shohei...
I only got to chat with him at dinner.
He's funny, isn't he?
-He is.
-Is he?
He got funnier once he started drinking.
Have you seen the theater room yet?
-Not yet.
-You haven't?
-Shall we check it out?
-Yeah.
-I want to see the guys' room.
-Yeah! Me too.
Let's go knock on their door.
-Shall we? I hope they're awake.
-Let's go.
Good point.
-If they're asleep...
-We'll wake them up?
Haruka must be really into cars
to be driving a Corvette.
-Good point.
-You think she's a car fanatic?
-Probably.
-I think so.
Those cars look intense.
They have that low profile
that you'd expect
from an American sports car.
I wonder if her personality
is intense as well, then.
I wonder.
I want her to clash with someone so badly.
She does seem strong-willed.
That scene when they were shopping
and left Risako behind...
-Oh, yeah!
-That was some crummy behavior.
-Don't you think?
-Agreed.
I can't wait to see
these little incidents pile up
and end in an explosion.
-That's what you're craving?
-Yeah. It'd be fantastic.
-I'm nursing that dream as we speak.
-Oh, dear.
You're turning into Kunie Tanaka.
"It'd be fantastic. I'm nursing it now."
-Complete the character with that beanie.
-You're so right.
Ladies, what are your impressions
of the guys?
Who do you like so far?
Shohei piques my interest.
He seems comforting to be around.
I can see him becoming popular.
But you're okay with that porn star vibe?
-The porn star vibe?
-That porn vibe in the guys' room.
He would be really popular
amongst the porn actresses.
That towel cemented the look.
That look was effortless on him.
Shohei's porn star vibe
is a respectable one.
-Agreed.
-100%.
He's not the sleazy adult film actor type.
What about you, Torichan?
I like Ruka-kun.
-What?
-Did you hear her?
Every time Ruka appeared,
she'd go, "So handsome."
So handsome.
-His profile is handsome, too.
-It really is.
Are you drawn to the androgynous type?
I love a guy with a sharp chin.
A sharp chin, huh?
The guys that Torichan falls for
in the beginning
tend to plummet in likability by the end.
According to Terrace House history.
-Everyone except Hansan.
-Only Hansan prevailed in character.
Do you really believe
he blushes out of shyness?
Yeah, that...
The women of Terrace House
seem to be taken by this quirk so far.
-They think it's cute.
-Irresistibly cute.
I really want Haruka
to take advantage of him
as she sees fit.
Of Ruka, I mean.
I can see the women using Ruka
for their own amusement.
-Shall we keep watching?
-Let's.
-The final block.
-We're already at the end!
That flew by.
Aren't we blessed that we can enjoy this
for the next year and a half?
-It's the best.
-Wonderful.
I might pare down my commitments
to just this show.
That's a simple life.
-Be a professional Terrace House watcher?
-Yeah.
-Everyone is awake!
-So they are.
Oh, great.
We'd like to see the guys' room.
-By all means.
-Huh?
-Go ahead.
-What?
-Be our guest.
-Huh?
Go take a look.
What? On our own?
-We can look by ourselves?
-All right, I'll lead the tour.
-Appreciate it.
-Thank you. It might be messy.
-Excuse us.
-Look at this mirror!
-I'm envious of this mirror.
-Right?
-Tons of space!
-Here it is.
Welcome to the guys' room.
-It's almost twice the size of ours.
-Very relaxing.
-Is it that big?
-Yeah.
Have you guys gotten to know each other?
We've bonded pretty quickly, yeah.
Conveniently, we're interested in
different people,
so there isn't much clashing.
The other two are pretty quiet,
aren't they?
-They are.
-Kind of reserved, right?
-Didn't you notice that during dinner?
-About the other two?
-Yeah, I thought so.
-Me, too.
-Right?
-Ruka is shy by nature, though.
-Yeah, he can't really help it.
-His quietness makes sense.
Kenny... Kenny...
They have a similar demeanor.
Perhaps he's quiet because of his age.
No, he's keeping a lot under wraps.
-Under wraps?
-He's holding back. That's my guess.
Do you guys all have plans
for the weekend?
-Not really.
-Not doing much, no.
You don't normally have weekends off?
-No, not necessarily.
-I see.
Actually...
I'm drawn to you, Kaori.
Very strongly.
Would you like to grab a drink
next time you're free?
-That sounds great.
-Maybe around Sangenjaya?
Yeah, let's check out Sancha.
Whenever our schedules align.
-Let's do it.
-I'd love to grab a drink with you.
-That was unexpected.
-Yeah. I'm happy.
-Thanks for having us.
-No problem.
-Shall we?
-Have a great night.
-Good night!
Night!
Good night.
I wonder if...
Shohei planned to be alone with us
so that he could ask you out.
He did volunteer himself
to show us the room.
Are you looking forward to it?
Yeah, I am.
-I'm not sure if it's a date, though.
-It's definitely a date.
-That was pretty clear.
-Remember, he said,
"I'm drawn to you. Strongly."
That's what I heard.
Emphasis on "strongly."
No doubt.
He caught me off guard, so it was
difficult to respond with a straight face.
-That's cute.
-I was like "Oh, my!"
I had to hide my face and be like, "Sure."