Hikigaya... you still have
one more request left.
Will you... listen to my request?
Okay. Let's hear it.
There was a long silence.
Someone said that it was because
it seemed like it'd be a long story.
It may have been me who said that.
Even if it was a short amount of time,
the glimmer of hope never strengthened.
I just knew that a definite answer
would spell a disasterous end.
If it isn't said out
loud, no one will get it.
Even if it's said, it won't be understood.
That's why it must be said out loud.
Even if you know that choice
will surely cause regret.
Because honestly, the only aunthenticity
I don't want is one that is cold, cruel, and sad.
That's very pretty.
Oh, yeah!
I searched for lots of different kinds of bags
and colorful masking tape!
Colorful "Namaste?" Isn't that
some sort of greeting in India?
Are you even listening? She
clearly said masking tape.
That's some particularly useless knowledge
for someone who doesn't even give a proper greeting.
Don't be dumb. A simple greeting
can create an atmosphere for conversation, right?
The standards of greeting
are essential knowledge.
A greeting counts as a conversation
to you, doesn't it?
Yes. That's why I try to do
it as little as possible.
Hikki, that's really bad.
I have no confidence in how it tastes,
but since I did do my best...
Yeah, I can understand that.
Right? That's what you told
me. I'm showing that I tried!
It's totally different from Yukino's.
How am I supposed to make you understand?
You know, I've been wondering
about something...
Why are you two trying to
make cookies that taste good?
Well, you know. Guys are simple.
They'll get the wrong idea if
you so much as talk to them,
and they'll be happy just to get
homemade cookies from you.
That's why it's fine!
As long as he knows you tried your best,
wouldn't that make him like you?
Would it work on you too, Hikki?
You remember that?
W-well, maybe. Not sure if I remembered,
or if I just couldn't forget.
I was kinda surprised at first.
B-but, you've always been like that, Hikki,
so I'm used to it.
Right, you're constantly
falling short of expectations.
That's true!
Uh, I don't think that only
applies to me, though.
Same goes for you, right,
Miss I'll-Do-Without?
What do you mean by that
questionable nickname?
W-well, I mean, you do have
a sort of clueless side, Yukinon.
Aren't you the clueless one?
That isn't true!
I am not!
Yes, you are.
No, I'm not!
It stopped snowing.
I heard it was snowing on the day I was born.
That's why my name is Yukino. Simple, right?
But it's a wonderful, beautiful name.
Yeah... It's a nice name.
Thanks.
My mom chose it.
Though, that's just what
I heard from my sister.
Yukinoshita, will you tell us about yourself?
I don't mind if you ask.
I always thought it'd be better to just wait.
Up to now, you've told us
stuff, little by little.
Yuigahama. You asked me what I wanted to do,
didn't you? But I don't really know.
A long time ago, there were things
I want to do, and things I wanted to do.
Huh? Things you wanted to do?
My dad's job.
But that's...
Right. Since I have an older sister,
I don't get to decide that.
My mother has always made the decisions.
For a long time now,
my mother has decided everything...
She tied my sister down,
and only told me to do what I wanted.
That's why I didn't know
how to conduct myself.
I still don't know, even now.
Yukino, do you have your own identity?
It's truly just like my sister said.
This is the first time
anyone's listened to me talk about this.
I see.
My mom and dad have hinted
at it before, I think.
I don't remember them addressing
it directly, though.
It may have been because my sister
was going to succeed my parents.
Haruno?
I don't think they ever said it.
You know what her personality is like.
Oh, I get it.
But they should have just told her that.
Even if that's not what she wants...
Maybe they were afraid to hear a proper answer
since they didn't check with her.
That's why I have to start by
verifying things with her...
...then the next time, I'll
decide on my own accord.
I won't do it because someone told me to,
but because I thought about it carefully,
accepted it, and decided to give up.
I have only one request.
I want the two of you
to see this through until very end.
That's all I want.
I guess that was your answer then, Yukinon...
I may be wrong about that...
Then in that case...
But, I...
I want to prove that I can do well on my own.
If I can do that, then I can truly start.
You can... truly start...
Yes. I'm going to go back home for a little while
and start talking about this from scratch.
We can consider that your answer, right?
I don't think you're wrong about that, but...
It doesn't hurt to give it a try, right?
Yeah, I get it. That would
count as an answer, too.
Thanks.
Let's get going.
Is You-know-who still there?
She might be.
Oh look, it's Yukino.
Sis...
Welcome home!
Were you drinking?
Well, kind of. Just a bit.
More importantly, does this mean you're back?
Yes.
There's something I need
to talk to you about.
Mornin'.
Hey.
Okay...
How's it looking?
Umm... It could look worse.
At this point in time, I'm going to have to do it
even if I'm kicking and screaming.
It's all basically decided
by yesterday's test, anyway.
Want to get something to eat together
after your interview?
Oh, that sounds good.
It does, right?
Yeah, yeah!
I can keep on pushing if I get rewarded
with a meal paid for by my brother, tee-hee-hee!
That line's gonna get me so
many points, tee-hee-hee!
I'm not treating you
and that didn't score you many points at all.
Well, it would be a date with my sister.
I can manage to at least pay for the meal.
Hm. Actually, if you're gonna call it a date,
then I definitely don't wanna go,
but if you're paying for both the meal
and transportation, then I can deal with it.
Oh man, stop with the serious face!
What do you mean "deal with it"?
That means you'd really hate to do it right?
You're the only one I say this sort of thing to
so it's fine, right? Do you not like it?
Ew, there's that creepy thing you do again.
Well, I'm heading out now.
All right, see you later.
Miraiya Bookstore
When I think of familiar young girls,
I think of Keika Kawasaki.
And, when I think of someone
completely coddling her,
I think of... that's
right, that Kawa-whoever!
Oh man, what the heck?! She's too cute!
Want a bite?
Yeah!
This is why I like you, Hachiman!
Yes, yes, I know you do.
But boys are going to immediately misunderstand
that sort of nonchalant touching,
so don't do that to anyone else, okay?
Okay! I'll only do that to you, Hachiman!
Oh man, if she used her girlish
charms as a terrorist,
she would already know the powerful words
that capture a man's heart!
This child is to be feared!
Whoa, what are you teaching her?
And that's kind of a problem.
Huh?
We haven't even had lunch yet.
Oh.
Uhh...
Okay, let's split it. But keep it a secret
from your sister.  Shhh...
Right! It's a secret! Shhh!
I'm looking right at you two.
Don't go spoiling her, though.
I-I don't, this is fine once in a while.
Once in a while is all
the time for you, right?
I don't think I do this all of the time.
I do this especially for Keika.
And for Komachi, too.
You have no loyalty, huh?
Yikes! I seriously just do not get girls!
Just a "Do you know why I'm mad?"
completely stumps me.
Don't fight.
We're not fighting. Turn this way, Keika.
Your brother is taking the entrance exam, too, right?
How was he doing?
I don't know. He'd always get
such an attitude when I'd ask about it.
Oh. He's at about that age, isn't he?
I personally wouldn't mind if he went to
a private school... I mean, if that's what he wants.
I see...
Considering next year,
you want to get into a public school, right?
Huh?
Your first choice for schools
is a national public school, right?
Just guessing, but you're probably
feeling some pressure from that.
You're talking about me?
No, no. Well, not far from
what I mean, but still wrong.
What is it then?
Uh, er, look... If your brother can go
to a public school, wouldn't that broaden
your choices, even if only a little?
Just guessing, though.
Tuition is completely different
for high school and university.
But... that seems like something he'd say.
Isn't it?
I'd understand having a sister complex
better than anyone, after all!
What are you talking about? That's creepy.
Creepy! Creepy!
Well, that's completely true...
It is really creepy.
I'm done! Yay!
Yay!
Saki and Keika, too! Hello, yay!
Y-yay...
Oh wow, I could barely hear that, Saki!
Let's try it again, yay!
Y-yay!
What is up with your sister?
Sorry about that. She seems
pretty hyper right now.
Komachi, have some water.
Drink this and calm down.
Thanks! But drinking from your cup
is kinda gross so I'm gonna go buy something.
Huh? Komachi?!
Just as close as ever, eh?
Uh, that's pretty much seriously untrue.
Komachi... Can you stop sounding so serious
when you're denying it?
To tell the truth, he's
super annoying sometimes!
K-Komachi.... Komachi!
Fine, just kidding, I totally love you.
What? That was a lie. A
complete and utter one.
I mean, I love you, too, though.
Ugh, gross. Gross. So gross.
Kawasaki!
Why are you breathing like that?
You were on the roof before, weren't you?
How did you get there?
You've got a good memory, huh...?
From the entrance at the central staircase.
The lock there is broken.
It's pretty well-known amongst the girls.
Why do you need to know that?
Thank you!
I love you, Kawasaki!
Ew, he's here, gross. So creepy!
Blushing like that towards your sister is gross!
Even though you're hopeless
and can only say that to
Wait, hey... Whoa, wait
y-you're going too far,
you're saying way too much.
your sister that facial expression
is creepy! So creepy!
Your verbal attacks are downright vulgar now.
Big Bro, that type of thing is for real gross.
You are truly talented in your grossness.
Aren't you even a little flattered?
I'm going to leave now. I
have to head home and cook.
Wanna go eat, too?
Did you think about what you wanted?
Yeah. I came up with a lot of stuff, but...
I wanna go home and do some chores!
Huh? What do you mean?
So now... Let's go shopping then go home!
Games
Batting Cages
Pool
Karaoke
Do you need a hand?
Nah, don't bother. Stay right where you are.
You'd just get in the way.
Ouch.
I mean, you're sloppy when you do things,
and you don't clean up when you cook.
Oh, yeah, you're right. I
sure don't, it's a pain.
Sorry, little maid girl.
Who's a maid? I'm just Komachi.
Besides, I want to do this, so it's fine.
I wasn't able to at all while studying for exams.
Here.
Thanks. I wanted to do
something, too, you know?
No, it's fine. This is my hobby.
What, chores?
Hm... Well, it's more like...
Pampering you is my hobby?
Oh no, what are you saying?
Are you my mom now?
Ko-mom-chi...
Ew, gross! Big Bro, are you sick?
Shut up, get off my back.
But you know, I could ask you the same thing.
You've got a pretty nice hobby.
I know, right? I get lots
of points for it, huh?
It's the greatest feeling to think about
how I can ruin someone with my own two hands...
You're sick, too, huh?
Tee-hee-hee!
But I really do like doing chores.
Oh?
How can I say this?
Unlike all those times when you
looked after me,
I'm able to do so many things now.
Maybe it's that there are things that even I can do,
or that I'm definitely being useful...
That sort of thing's not bad.
It's not a question of being not too bad...
If anything you're way too capable now.
Well, that's because I worked hard for this!
The sense of impending
doom you feel when you
have a useless older brother
makes you grow up really fast!
I know! I'm the ultimate example
of how not to live, aren't I?
And you've grown even more!
You should be grateful to me for that.
Right, I am grateful.
Huh?
This is probably something I should do
after I've actually passed the exam.
It'd be embarrassing to say it
again if I pass, and if I fail then
it won't feel like the right time for it.
Now is the only time I can say this, so...
Thanks, Big Brother.
Thank you for doing so much for me.
You dummy, what are you talking about?
This is embarassing, stop it.
I just wanted to try saying it.
I thought I could get a lot of points for this.
You won't get a lot of points, and besides,
it looks like you're off to become someone's bride.
Nope. I'd never allow you
to get married or anything, and...
And also... What? For real, stop...
There's like, water coming from my eyes...
What is this? What? Why is this happening?
Those are tears. Big Bro, you're like a robot
understanding emotions for the first time.
These are... tears. These are... emotions.
Why are you talking like
that all of a sudden?
I'm going to go warm the
bath and then hop in.
Big Bro!
She's distancing herself from me now, huh?
What do you think about this, Kamakura?
In Due Time, the Seasons Change
and the Snow Melts.
It's a bit too early to graduate, huh?
Komachi! Koma...chi...
Komachi was quite the handful
when she was little, too!  And it was... just so...
Big Bro the bath is re-
Whoa, why are you crying so much?
No, you dummy, I'm not crying!
This is sweat, just sweat.
Talking to people makes me sweaty.
But you were talking to a cat.
Are you okay? Do you want to go to therapy?
Therapy makes me sweaty, too, so no.
I'm gonna go take a bath!
And this is why you're trash.
Oh, well. Guess I have to take care of him
for a while longer!
That Key
Was Never Handled
Until Today.