So I heard about it.
Seems like it was really rough.
Do you feel like a weight got
lifted off of your shoulders?
Huh? From what?
Oh, you mean my sister?
No, not that.
I'm sure that was rough, too, though.
Oh, yeah. Will you tell your sister congrats
on finishing her exams for me?
No, why would I?
Why do I have to give her a message from you?
Though I'm happy to hear
you say that. Thanks.
Unbelievable, I never thought
I'd get thanked like that.
I wasn't referring to your
little sister, though…
I meant that other little sister.
There's something I want
to talk to you about.
Okay.
First of all, would you like to come in?
You're going to drink more?
Of course. There are some
days I just want to drink.
Besides, alcohol helps make life
go down a bit smoother.
I think it's more often the
root cause of problems, though.
Don't worry, I'll listen
to what you have to say.
Right. You won't listen to
me even when you're sober.
This is true! Now then…
What did you wanna say?
I wanted to talk about us,
and what will happen with us in the future.
Oh?
You're going to let me in on all that?
Yes.
This is about you and me. And also about Mom.
Ah, that's what you meant.
This doesn't sound like
something I want to hear.
Right?
I still want you to listen.
That's why I'm going home.
There, I will talk to Mom about
my future and what I want.
Even if I can't get what I want,
I don't want to have any regrets.
I want to... at least make myself clear,
so that I can accept the outcome.
I see. So I guess that's your answer, then.
Well, that's fine. You've
grown a little, I guess.
I know what you want to say.
If you're serious about it, then I'll work with you.
You'll work with me?
Yes.
Mom's not the type of person
to change course very easily.
So I'll put in a good word
for you when appropriate.
That being said, I don't know
if that will be effective or not.
However, you should go there with the assumption
that you won't be back here for awhile.
I figured.
Huh?
I was only allowed to come here
because she was worried about Yukino.
If Yukino goes home,
she probably won't be set free again so easily.
First, pack up your things.
Then you'll need to get in touch with Mom.
Yes… I'll do that.
Hey.
So I'll have free use of this
place for awhile. That okay?
You can do what you want with it.
Thanks.
I'll help you pack up, too!
No, I can't let you do that for me, too…
It's totally okay! I actually want you to let me help.
I really like organizing things!
But…
I think this is the only thing
I'm able to help you with…
Let her do it.
Free labor is hard to find nowadays.
That sounds good.
Why don't you go ahead and stay the night?
Would that be… asking too much?
No, I'd love to!
Thanks.
Let's do some decluttering! I recently bought
a ton of books on how to declutter!
Those books are the first thing
that should be decluttered.
I'm going to the convenience store.
Do you need anything?
I thought you went to the convenience store.
This sort of thing feels a bit
like a rendezvous, doesn't it?
Isn't this more like an ambush?
It's freezing.
Hmm…
Oh, cigarette smoke, huh?
Yeah.
You were drinking for quite some time, huh?
Yep, they wouldn't let me go home.
I almost got pulled into
going at it all night.
O-oh...
But I'm so glad I came home early.
I was able to listen to what Yukino had to say.
Hm?
Er, that's just kind of surprising.
What is?
That you actually listened to her.
Of course I did.
I'm still her older sister, after all.
If that's what Yukino has chosen, then I will support
that decision, whether it's the right one or not.
If she's making the wrong
choice, shouldn't you stop her?
She wouldn't listen to me.
More importantly, I don't care either way.
Because nothing will change.
Whether it works out or she gives up.
Everybody becomes an adult by giving up
on various things like that, you know.
Ah, I see…
Do you have that sort of experience?
Hm, I wonder!
I don't matter here. We're
talking about Yukino right now.
I think this is the first time
she's ever made herself clear.
Please watch over her too, Hikigaya.
I will.
I acted like a big sister again…
Why don't you try being
like that all the time?
No way. I'm not like you.
You're always acting like a big brother.
Well, yeah… I am a big brother after all.
Oh, I see…
It must be nice to have an older brother like you.
I wish I had one of those!
Hey…You're being an
annoying drunk right now.
Oh no, I'm not drunk!
Er… Can you make it home okay?
Oh, you're so kind! A gentleman, even!
I'm not a gentleman. I plan
on going straight home.
I'm fine.
No way I'd get drunk from that.
That sounds like something drunk people say.
I'm telling you, I'm really not drunk.
Maybe I can't get drunk.
No matter how much alcohol I drink,
a part of me always stays calm.
I can even see what kind of face I'm making.
Even if I laugh and get wild,
I feel like it's not actually me doing it.
You're probably the same.
I'm calling it right now.
Well, I think the hard part starts now.
Just guessing, though.
I agree.
But it's a whole lot better
than it was before.
I thought she would never change.
You're probably the same.
I'm calling it right now.
You can't get drunk.
You surprised me!
Oh, s-sorry…
But you scare too easily!
So?
Wanna go to the club?
Yeah. For now, I mean…
By the way, why do you have that blanket?
Blanket? Oh you mean the one for my lap?
Oh, for your lap, huh?
Didn't you have a different one before?
You pay more attention
to me than I thought...
N-no… N-not especially
or anything, I just…
Anyways, why'd you buy a new blanket
even though you already have one?
How many laps do you have?
Are you a centipede?
No, I'm not!
I bought a magazine and this
came with it! That's it!
I guess I do that a lot, because I
realized I have too many blankets
and don't know what to do with them.
R-right…
Maybe, if our club continues for a little longer,
I was thinking I'd leave it in the room…
If it continues, huh?
It's still locked.
I guess Yukinon hasn't come yet.
I'll go get the key.
Huh? U-um, wait…
Staff Room
Hey, Hikigaya.
What's up?
I came to get the key for our club room.
Oh.
Well, Yukinoshita already came
and took the key earlier.
That's why I said I'd call her.
Uh, I don't think you said that.
That's cause you left before I said it!
I went ahead and made tea…
Would you like some?
Yeah.
Um… About the other day...
Thanks.
Did you finish the move okay?
Yes. I wouldn't go as far as
to call it "moving," though…
And Yuigahama was there to help me.
Oh, yeah, not a problem! It was no big deal.
You really helped me out. Thanks.
Come in.
Excuse me!
So, I borrowed a DVD, but the student council laptop
is too new and doesn't even play DVDs!
What is this?
It's quite small, but
it's a projector, right?
It is!
Apparently, it can even display
videos off a smartphone.
Oh, but it's expensive, right?
Well, get this!
It came entirely out of the student council
budget, which comes at zero personal cost to me!
That was the worst
product demo sales presentation ever.
Ah, wait, I'm gonna put the screen up!
Wow, that was great!
So tell me, why were you
watching a movie here?
Huh? It's not a movie, it's a TV drama.
That part doesn't matter…
I was watching it for reference.
But if I watched it in the student council room,
I would seem like I'm slacking off.
What does that say about the fact
you chose to watch it here?
Watch it at home!
I follow the principle of not working
outside of designated hours!
By the way, what do you mean by "reference?"
There's a graduation
ceremony this year, right?
And then something called a
thank-you party or something?
The student council has
to manage all of that.
Right, the thank-you party.
Well, to be honest, a normal
thank-you party is fine,
but when I think about the
one from when I graduated,
I'd like to make something
more flashy for this one.
Um.. And I think the graduates
would be happy with it, too.
I see.
And that's why you want the prom.
Yeah! You always just get it
Yukinoshita! You're so great!
A pro…? What's that?
A promenade, otherwise known as a prom.
Put simply, it's an abbreviation
for a type of dance.
In high schools overseas,
it's the last dance party of the school year.
Oh! There was a scene like
that in the drama, too!
Uh, why not just do a normal one?
Why do you want to make it a prom?
Because, I'm going to be the prom queen!
Oh…
That was in the drama, too.
That scene where they were like
"let's choose
the hottest boy and girl in our year!" or whatever.
For our grade, the prom king
would undoubtedly be Hayama.
Yeah, that's probably true!
Basically, Hayama will be the
king, and I'll be the qu-
By the way, Hikigaya, this is totally unrelated,
but are you going to get held back a year?
As if.
Oh, come on!
It'd be the same as spending a year
waiting to retake university entrance exams right?
And using your student discount
is always a great bargain, you know?
Don't assign that future to me.
Besides, I'd lose way more than I'd save.
Okay, what if you help with
the prom instead, then?
Instead of? Instead of what?
So, are you seriously going to hold a prom?
Yes!
But it definitely can't happen
even if you start it now.
I think it looks like fun,
but… it also looks difficult.
That's right.
Well…
I know that.
But I want to do it… Do you
think that's unacceptable?
It's not a matter of acceptability,
but more that it's not really doable.
There are a multitude of reasons why,
but… I mean, you understand that, right?
I see.
Okay.
Then the student council will
try to do this on our own.
Right, good decision… Huh?
Were you listening?
Yes. So we're going to do it on our own.
O-okay. Alright then.
If you change your mind or gain an interest,
come hang out in the student council room!
You're always welcome!
So much that we won't let you go!
She just wants to run us ragged, doesn't she?
Can I ask you something?
Yes?
Why do you want to do so much to hold a prom?
Huh?
Um, because, I mean, I
want to be prom queen…
You mean in two years, right?
Yeah, well…
I've gotta start laying the
groundwork for that now.
Supposing that a prom is
held two years from now,
you'll be chosen as queen
even if you don't lay any groundwork today.
U-um... What?!
I'm saying there's no real reason
you have to do this right now.
Even next year, there will be no problem…
That won't work!
Even if I suggest holding a prom next year,
it probably wouldn't happen.
We'll be forced to give up
because they'll say we won't have enough time.
That's why no matter how difficult
it is, and even if it's a flop,
I have to lay the foundations
for my next move!
Isshiki…
This has to be done now.
If we start now, we may be ready in time.
What and who are you doing this for?
For myself, of course!
Right. Thank you for your answer.
Now then, let's get started.
Wha-? Huh?
Are you for real gonna do it?
Oh my gawd, Yukinoshita! I freakin' love you!
Hold on…
But what was with the third-degree
you just gave me? It was scary!
It'd be great if you'd stop
doing stuff like that!
Well, I guess we have no choice
if that's what the president has decided.
We'll do our job.
Yep, we will.
Um, can I speak with you two?
Huh?
What I just did was on
my own personal volition.
I have no intention of forcing you to help.
O-okay. What do you mean?
In other words, well… this was not a decision
I made as club president,
so I don't have the authority
to make you help.
But of course, I would be grateful
to receive help from you two…
Simply, even if it's on my own,
I intend to take responsibility for the prom
and see it through to completion.
Or rather…
You mean we're free to participate or not?
No, Hikki.
Yukinon is saying that she wants to try
to do this on her own, right?
This has to be done now…
If we start now, we may be ready in time.
Maybe… That applies to me, too.
Because...
I want to make a proper start.
I'd be happy if you two would watch over me.
Then I won't say a word. But promise me,
you will absolutely not overexert yourself.
And if you need manpower
then you have to call us.
Even if it's not as the Service Club,
you can call us as your friends.
I want to help you when that happens.
Yes, I promise I will.
Thanks.
Alright! Sounds good to
me! How about you, Hikki?
Same.
Am I making a mistake?
No, this sounds fine. No idea, though.
You never say anything helpful.
I get it, for the most part!
Okay then, thanks for your help, Yukino!
What did she just call you?
I'm looking forward to this.
Then will you please come
to the student council room starting tomorrow?
Sure, I don't mind.
Thank you!
Forget about it.
Act like you didn't see it.
Yukinon.
Are you taking this coat with you?
No, I don't need it.
'Kay!
Haruno
I'll be back.
Hello.
We should have some mineral water left.
I actually realized it a long time ago.
There was a place that I couldn't get into,
and though I stand in front of
that door time and time again,
I get the feeling that
I shouldn't disturb it.
All I can do is peek in through
a crack and eavesdrop…
Actually, I realized it a long time ago.
I knew I wanted to go there.
I wanted nothing more than that.
That's why, honestly…
That Key Was Never Handled
Until Today.
I never wanted anything genuine.
You like chick flick movies
like that, don't you?
Well, isn't it a relief
that I prefer chick flicks?
Women who say they prefer
Hollywood action blockbusters
are only saying that to
appease their boyfriends.
What? Is that true?
In nine cases out of ten, yes.
Hey, stop it.
You're breaking the hearts
of all the guys out there
who think their girlfriends
actually like the same movies.
Okay. But evil women always
pull moves like that to-
Wait, were you just hitting on me?
Did you say that because you were going
to invite me on a movie date after this?
I'm sorry I ruined it.
Iroha Isshiki is the Strongest Junior,
as Expected.
Seriously? There's no point now…